Yes, I do smell a rat. And I'd like to
know why no one in the media is talking
about the investigation or the fact that
there should have been an investigation
into whether or not Jeffrey Epstein was
working for a foreign intelligence
service. You know, let's
So, so that's really interesting. So,
look, you you've studied into this. What
is the evidence that he might have been?
He is the a textbook example of an of an
access agent. You're, like I said the
last time I was on the show, Pierce,
you're not going to recruit Bill
Clinton. You're not going to recruit
Bill Gates. You're not going to recruit
Alan Dersowitz, but you can recruit
someone who gets close to those people.
You can give them something that you can
hold over their heads if you have to in
the end, and then you report back to
your handlers everything that they say.
And in exchange, you get untold wealth
and a house in the Caribbean and the the
biggest townhouse in Manhattan and a
private plane. And that's a pretty good
life, especially if you're a pedophile
and you enjoy doing things like that.
And nobody's talking about whether or
not he was an access agent.
Yeah. I mean, that's really interesting.
I mean, does the intelligence community
believe that there is merit to that
suggestion?
Yes, it does. It does. But the problem
here is the accusation is that he was an
access agent for the Israelis. And
that's something that the intelligence
community really doesn't like to touch.
Why?
Because we have this special
relationship with Israel. Not like a
five eyes relationship like we have with
the UK, Canada, Australia, New Zealand,
but this special relationship where we
share so much. We provide so much. We
work with the Israelis on issues all
around the region, at least around the
world. on a handful of issues. Why upset
the balance over one dead pedophile?
Isn't it easier just to cover it up?
Brian, what do you think of that?
Um, I I I believe that Jeffrey Epstein
surrounded himself with a lot of uh
powerful people. It is very very
possible that he could have been working
for a government agency. Very very
possible. as well. I I would tend to
agree with the fact that this needs to
be investigated more. The media needs to
talk about it more. And I don't think
this is just a situation where Jeffrey
Epstein was getting people to come on
his island and sadly do horrible things
to young girls. I think there's a lot
more to this story. I think there's a
lot of people hiding a lot of
information. So, I I certainly agree
with what he just said. I mean, um,
Jack, one of the I mean, one of the
conspiracy theories I've seen online a
lot in the last few days is it's not a
coincidence that Netanyahu is coming to
the White House, that he's been there, I
think, three times in the last few
months, that he has a much better
relationship with Trump now than they
did when he uh pissed Trump off by, you
know, going to see Biden and so on. Um,
and that suddenly the Epstein files
disappear. if you were working as a
conspiracy theorist and you bought into
the idea that he was some kind of agent
for the Israelis, which is not
completely implausible um given all the
connections he had and know has there
been some tacit agreement with Netanyahu
to get rid of this problem? I mean,
stranger things have happened.
I think the perception is horrible. I
think the perception is absolutely
horrible and uh it puts a huge huge onus
on the entire administration and
certainly coming from Pam Bondi for her
mismanagement of this. I wanted to go
back to something that John was saying
as well, but uh Galileain Maxwell's
father Robert uh this is some so Robert
Maxwell is someone who's highly fingered
in a lot of these conspiracies or a lot
of these allegations. his entire career,
there were allegation after allegation
that he was involved somehow with
Israeli intelligence going all the way
back even to the 1940s and serious
questions about some of the work that he
did all the way through this. And then
of course, as it goes, she becomes the
recruiter for Epstein. And so these
questions have really gone deeper and
deeper and deeper. And of course,
there's no actual evidence or, you know,
just hearing of the evidence or release
of the evidence, release of the file, a
task force, even a press conference, you
know, and instead we get, oh, well,
we're just going to move on and here's a
press release on a, you know, on a
Sunday night when it's, you know, it's a
holiday here in the